## **Noah Bressner**

# nhbressner@gmail.com • (845) 499-0883 215 E 88th St., Apt. 4B, New York, NY 10128

#### SUMMARY

As an editor with three years of experience working on the New York Post's web team, I leverage the Post's unique voice to create eyecatching and informative packages for our website, app and other digital platforms. My responsibilities there cover everything from troubleshooting technical issues and fielding questions from co-workers to managing the home page with the help of audience analytics.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **New York Post**

Associate Digital Editor

November 2020 - Present

- Use audience data and news judgment to curate nypost.com and the NY Post app
- Edit and publish stories to ensure copy, headlines, photos, captions, videos and other assets drive engagement
- Write and send email alerts and push notifications for both the app and browser
- Coordinate the workflow of breaking news and feature stories with editors from across the newsroom
- Manage digital producers to keep content on track and troubleshoot issues that arise during the publishing process
- Teach best practices for web publishing when working with journalists in other departments

Reporter/Producer

July 2019 - November 2020

- Copy edited stories, wrote headlines, selected photographs and produced videos while optimizing for SEO
- Identified and flagged emerging stories and reviewed push notifications to support breaking news coverage

Associate Reporter/Producer

August 2018 - July 2019

- Reported and wrote breaking news stories for news and sports desks that have collectively generated 5.9 million page views
- Contributed to the New York Post and New York Post Sports Facebook and Twitter accounts using SocialFlow

Digital Intern

June 2018 - August 2018

December 2017 - May 2018

• Pitched, reported and wrote stories for the digital news and sports editors

#### Pipe Dream, Binghamton University

Editor in Chief

- Coordinated operations and production of twice-weekly independent student newspaper with a circulation of 7,000
- Approved all published content and oversaw business operations that brought in yearly advertising revenue of about \$90,000
- Supervised staff of 150+ editors, reporters, designers, photographers, business staff and developers

Other Positions: Managing Editor (June 2017-December 2017), Assistant Sports Editor (June 2016-June 2017)

#### **WIVT/WBGH News Channel 34**

June 2017 - August 2017

News Intern

Pitched, reported and filmed compelling local news stories for the NBC and ABC affiliate in Binghamton, N.Y.

# **New York State Division of Human Rights**

August 2016 - December 2016

Human Rights Intern

Reviewed claims of employment and housing discrimination by interviewing complainants and witnesses, assessing the merits of
cases, making probable cause determinations and writing drafts of final investigative reports

## Cardiothoracic Surgery Research Unit at Newark Beth Israel Medical Center

Summer 2015 & Summer 2016

Data Intern

- Analyzed data, focusing on Transcatheter Aortic Valve Replacement (TAVR), using Microsoft Excel and R for Dr. Mark J. Russo
- Supported submission process for scholarly medical journal articles and helped with other administrative tasks

## **EDUCATION**

## Binghamton University, State University of New York

May 2018

Bachelor of Arts in History

## **SKILLS**

Methode, R, HTML, CSS, WordPress, Parse.ly, Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe InDesign, Adobe Audition